[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long was the opening scene of the movie Scream?", "correct_answer": "12 mins", "incorrect_answers": ["11 mins", "10 mins", "9 mins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did King Oedipus marry his mother according to the Greek legend?", "correct_answer": "He didnt known she was his mother.", "incorrect_answers": ["To keep their riches withing the family", "Because he fell in love with her", "Because the gods forced him to do it"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed gang leader Frank Miller in High Noon?", "correct_answer": "Ian MacDonald", "incorrect_answers": ["Ian MacAllister", "Ian McDonald", "Ian Holm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first Ewok you see in Star Wars is called Wicket W Warrick.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Malone, this actor played Charles Delaney, a local bigwig bent on taking land throughout the area in a patriotic real estate scheme.", "correct_answer": "Cliff Robertson", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Stack", "Michael Douglas", "William Devane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Central Common Chimpanzee, native to Cameroon, is known to be the origin of which of the viruses causing AIDS?", "correct_answer": "HIV-1", "incorrect_answers": ["HIV-2", "All of these", "HIV-3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest fish in existence?", "correct_answer": "Whale shark", "incorrect_answers": ["Manta ray", "Ocean sunfish", "Basking shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the United Kingdom, when is the wedding breakfast served?", "correct_answer": "at the wedding reception", "incorrect_answers": ["in the morning after the wedding", "in the morning before the wedding", "the day before the wedding"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these nominated movies was the winner of the Oscar for Best Picture at the 48th Academy Award ceremony in 1976?", "correct_answer": "One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest", "incorrect_answers": ["Jaws", "Dog Day Afternoon", "Barry Lyndon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The director and the lead actor of this 2nd top grossing movie of 1991 share the same first name, Kevin.", "correct_answer": "Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves", "incorrect_answers": ["The Untouchables", "The Bodyguard", "For Love of the Game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The USA owns a territory in the Pacific called  The Commonwealth of the Northern Mariana Islands. What is its capital city?", "correct_answer": "Saipan", "incorrect_answers": ["Pago Pago", "Agana", "Charlotte Amalie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which skeletal muscle moves the scapula forward, as in pushing something?", "correct_answer": "Serratus anterior", "incorrect_answers": ["Soleus", "Sartorius", "Sternocleidomastoid"]}]